Well, that was fun.
(Sheldon:)Tomorrow we can go
to one of those warehouse stores.
(Penny:)I don't know, Sheldon.
It's gonna take me a while to recover
from all the fun I had today.
Are you sure? There are a lot
of advantages to buying in bulk.
(Sheldon:)For example, I noticed
you purchase your tampons...
(Sheldon:)...one month's supply at a time.
- What?
- Well, think about it.
It doesn't spoil...
(Sheldon:)...and you're going to be needing them
for at least the next 30 years.
(Penny:)You want me to buy
30 years' worth of tampons?
Well, 30, 35...
(Sheldon:)- When did your mother go into menopause?
- Okay.
(Penny:)I'm not talking about this with you.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Penny.
(Sheldon:)This is a natural human process
and we're talking about significant savings.
(Sheldon:)Now, if you assume 15 tampons per cycle
in a 28-day cycle...
(Sheldon:)Are you fairly regular?
(Sheldon:)Okay, no warehouse store,
but we're still on for putt-putt golf, right?